MAAD's mission is to stop drunk driving, support the victims of this violent crime, and to prevent underage drinking.
That is a very comprehensive mission, but it is also very focused at the same time.
We go in and we work with law enforcement, we work with families, we work with hospitals.
We work with all kinds of other service organizations to go in and try and stop drunk driving.
We go in with the prevention part of it, underage drinking, too.
The earlier, studies show, the earlier that youth actually consume alcohol, which on average now is about twelve years old, the more likely they are to have a dependency problem or to have drunk driving in their future.
So we try and go in and get to the root of the problem.
We start with our programs in early youth and we continue those throughout, outreach throughout the community throughout the entire year.
To try and make sure we're accomplishing our goals.
MAAD, on a national level since we began in 1980, we're saying our estimates show that we've been able to save 330,000 lives.
That's though working with legislation, that's through working with education, that's with working with judicial system and law enforcement.
Those are our four kind of main pillars that we've got.
And we're making a huge impact.
You can see across the United States that it is visible and we are out there trying to make a difference and save lives.